<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <descript>
            <abstract>The following is excerpted from an online document produced by the U.S. Census Bureau pertaining to cartographic boundary files of congressional districts:&amp;quot;Congressional districts (CDs) are the 435 areas from which people are elected to the U.S. House of Representatives. After the apportionment of congressional seats among the states, based on census population counts, each state is responsible for establishing CDs for the purpose of electing representatives. Each CD is to be as equal in population to all other CDs in the state as practicable.The CDs in effect at the time of Census 2000 were those of the 106th Congress, whose session began in January 1999. The boundaries were identical to those reflected in the 107th CD boundary files. The CDs for the 103rd Congress (January 1993 to 1995) were the first to reflect redistricting based on the 1990 census. The 103rd CDs remained in effect through Census 2000, except where a state initiative or a court-ordered redistricting required a change. Six states redistricted for the 104th Congress (Georgia, Louisiana, Maine, Minnesota, South Carolina, and Virginia), five states redistricted for the 105th Congress (Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Louisiana, and Texas), and three states (New York, North Carolina, and Virginia) redistricted for the 106th Congress. In North Carolina the &amp;quot;1998 Congressional Plan A&amp;quot; was used for the 1998 congressional elections. It was created in response to a court ruling which held the 1997 plan, &amp;quot;97 House/Senate Plan A,&amp;quot; unconstitutional. These boundaries are reflected in the 106th CD boundary files. The Supreme Court has since reversed that lower court ruling and the 1997 plan, &amp;quot;97 House/Senate Plan A,&amp;quot; (reflected in the 107th CD boundary files) was used for the 2000 North Carolina congressional elections. The 108th Congress is the first to reflect reapportionment and redistricting based on Census 2000 data.&amp;quot;</abstract>
            <purpose>CONGRESS_DISTRICTS_111TH_USCB_IN.SHP was created to provide a GIS data layer of the Indiana districts of the 111th congress. This data was downloaded from maps.indiana.edu and republished by IGIO staff on 12/15/2023.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <spdom>
            <bounding>
                <westbc>-88.1202823529337</westbc>
                <eastbc>-84.6882536907887</eastbc>
                <northbc>41.7811796455715</northbc>
                <southbc>37.7554022498442</southbc>
            </bounding>
        </spdom>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Congress</themekey>
                <themekey>Congress District (CD)</themekey>
                <themekey>111th Congress</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>It is requested that the Indiana Geological Survey be cited in any products generated from this data. The following source citation should be included: CONGRESS_DISTRICTS_111TH_USCB_IN: Indiana Districts for the 111th Congress (United States Census Bureau, 1:500,000, Polygon Shapefile), digital representation by Chris Dintaman, 2009.LIMITATION OF WARRANTIES AND LIABILITY - This product is provided &amp;quot;AS IS&amp;quot;, without any other warranties or conditions, expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, warranties for product quality, or suitability to a particular purpose or use. The risk or liability resulting from the use of this product is assumed by the user. The Indiana Geographic Information Office shares no liability with product users indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages whatsoever, including, but not limited to, loss of revenue or profit, lost or damaged data or other commercial or economic loss. The Indiana Geographic Information Office is not responsible for claims by a third party.</useconst>
        <datacred>Indiana Geological &amp; Water Survey (IGWS), United States Census Bureau</datacred>
    </idinfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
